Inventaris van het archief van het Ministerie van Economische Zaken: Directoraat-Generaal voor de Buitenlandse Economische Betrekkingen (vergaderstukken van internationale organisaties), 1945-1967
Nationaal Archief, Den Haag
- GENERAL AGREEMENT ON TARIFFS AND TRADE (GATT), 1948-heden.
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1961; 2127
    L/1452 - L/1562
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1961; 2128
    L/1563-L/1657
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1961-1962; 2129
    L/1658 - L/1757
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1962; 2130
    L/1758 - L/1804
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1962; 2131
    L/1805 - L/1876
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1962; 2132
    L/1877 - L/1939
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1962-1963; 2133
    L/1949 - L/1984
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1963; 2134
    L/1985 - L/2084
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1963-1964; 2135
    L/2085 - L/2171
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1964; 2136
    L/2171 - L/2294
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1964-1965; 2137
    L/2295 - L/2357
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1965; 2138
    L/2358 - L/2455
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1965; 2139
    L/2456 - L/2528
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT) (SR)7., 1952; 2140
    SR/7/1 - SR/7/17
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1953; 2140
    SR/8/1 - SR/8/21
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1954; 2140
    SR/9/1 - SR/9/28
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1955; 2141
    SR/9/29-SR/9/47
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1955; 2141
    SR/10/1 - SR/10/21
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1956; 2141
    SR/11/1 - SR/11/13
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1956; 2142
    SR/11/14-SR/11/18
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1957; 2142
    SR/12/1 - SR/12/22
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1 958; 2142
    SR/13/1 - SR/13/21
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1959; 2142
    SR/14/1 - SR/14/11
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1960-1961; 2143
    SR/15/1 - SR/15/18
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1960; 2143
    SR/16/1 - SR/16/11
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1960-1961; 2143
    SR/17/1 - SR/17/12
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1961; 2143
    SR/18/1 - SR/18/6
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1961-1962; 2144
    SR/19/1 - SR/19/12
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1962-1963; 2144
    SR/20/1 - SR/20/13
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1964; 2144
    SR/21/1 - SR/21/11
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1945; 2145
    Comm/2/1/2 - Comm/2/ A - Z
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1959-1960; 2146
    Comm/2/14 - Comm/2/39/add. 2
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1960; 2146
    Comm/2/40 - Comm/2/45
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1960; 2147
    Comm/2/46 - Comm/2/81
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1960; 2148
    Comm/2/86 - Comm/2/109
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1961; 2149
    Comm/2/110 - Comm/134
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1957; 2150
    W/12/1 - W/12/62
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1958; 2150
    W/13/1 - W/13/59
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1952; 2151
    W/7/1 - W/7/64
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1953; 2151
    W/8/1 - W/8/34
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1954-1955; 2152
    W/9/1 -W/9/153
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1955; 2153
    W/9/153 - W/9/239
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1955; 2154
    W/10/1 - W/10/53
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1956; 2154
    W/11/1 - W/11/36
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1959; 2154
    W/15/1 - W/15/43
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1959; 2155
    W/14/1 - W/36
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1960; 2155
    W/16/1 - W/16/28
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1960; 2155
    W/17/1 - W/17/48
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1961; 2155
    W/19/1 - W/19/26
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1952-1954; 2156
    G/1-G/79
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1954-1955; 2157
    G/80 - G/99
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1952; 2157
    IC/1 - IC/8
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1952-1953; 2157
    IC/SR/1 - IC/SR/11
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1951-1952; 2157
    IW/2/1 -IW/2/16
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1952-1953; 2157
    IC/W/1 - ICW/23
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1957-1958; 2157
    IC/WP/1/1 -IC/WP1/11
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1958; 2158
    IC/WP/11 - IC/WP/37
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950-1953; 2158
    Press release 1 - 120
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1953-1955; 2159
    Press release 121 - 299
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1956-1959; 2160
    Press release 300 - 477
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1959-1961; 2161
    Press release 437 - 676
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1962-1963; 2162
    Press release 677-744
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1963; 2162
    Press release ministersconf.
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1956-1957; 2162
    QRC/1 - QRC/24
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1957; 2163
    QRC 1 - 30
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1963; 2163
    AC/l - 7
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1960-1961; 2163
    C 1 - 18
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1962; 2163
    CG 1 - 3
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1960-1961; 2163
    CM 1 - 8
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1957; 2164
    LA/SR 1
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1957; 2164
    CRT/SR 1 - CRT/SR 5
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1960-1961; 2164
    CW 1 - CW 31
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1954-1960; 2164
    IC/SR 12 - IC/SR 49
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1954-1955; 2164
    IC/W 24 - IC/W 39
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1955-1958; 2165
    IC/W 40 - IC/W 84
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1949; 2165
    A/INF/4 - A/INF/5
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1949-1951; 2165
    CP/INF 1 - CP/INF/3
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950-1951; 2165
    CP/5 A - W/1
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950; 2165
    IC/INF 1 - IC/INF 17
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950; 2165
    T 40.57
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950-1951; 2165
    T 60.81
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950-1951; 2166
    T/INF 1 - T/INF 99
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1949; 2166
    TN/1/SR 1 - TN/1/SR 10
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1948-1949; 2166
    TN 1/1 - TN 1/39
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1949; 2166
    TN 1/ A - TN 1/C
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950; 2166
    TN2/ A en B
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1949-1951; 2167
    TN/2/1 - TN2/44
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950-1951; 2167
    TN.2SR.1 - TN2/SR 10
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950-1951; 2167
    TN.2/secret/1 - TN.2/secret 17
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1956; 2167
    TN.56 div.
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1962; 2167
    TN.60/19 - TN.60/25
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1960-1961; 2167
    TN.60/SR.1 - TN.60/SR 14
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1960-1961; 2168
    TN.60/INF.1 - TN.60/INF 8
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1956-1958; 2168
    TNB/1 - TNS/INF 4
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1955; 2168
    TNJ/1 - TNJ/10 en TNJ/W 1 - 9
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1951; 2168
    SIX/1 - SIX/15
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1952; 2168
    SEVEN 1 - SEVEN 8
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1953; 2168
    EIGHT 1 - EIGHT 15
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1954; 2168
    NINE 1 - NINE 10
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1955; 2168
    TEN 1 - TEN 5
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1956; 2168
    ELEVEN 1 - ELEVEN 7
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1957; 2168
    TWELVE 1 - TWELVE 5
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1958; 2169
    THIRTEEN 1 - THIRTEEN 5
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1959; 2169
    FOURTEEN 1 - 2
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1959; 2169
    FIFTEEN 1 - 10
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1948-1950; 2169
    CP/1 - CP/61
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950-1951; 2170
    CP/62 - CP/114
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1951-1952; 2171
    CP/115 - CP/145
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1948; 2171
    CP/1 - CP/45 (CP2)
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1948; 2171
    CP2/SR 1 - CP/SR/25
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1948; 2171
    CP2/WP 1 - CP 2/WP
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1948-1949; 2172
    CP/3/1 - CP3/60
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1949; 2173
    CP3/61 - CP3/92
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1949; 2173
    CP3/SR/1 - CP3/SR/44
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1949; 2173
    CP3/various
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1949; 2174
    CP3/WP1 - CP3/WP10
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950; 2174
    CP4/SR1 - CP4/SR21
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1949-1950; 2174
    CP4/1 - CP4/45
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950; 2175
    CP4/1NF 1 - CP4/INF/6
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950; 2175
    CP4/A/1 - CP4/H/3
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950; 2175
    CP5/1 - CP5/52
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950; 2175
    CP5/SR/1 - CP5/SR26
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1951; 2175
    CP6/1 - CP6/12
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1951; 2176
    CP6/13 - CP6/56
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1951; 2176
    CP6/SR 1 - CP6/SR 27
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1951; 2176
    CP6/W/1-CP6W/12
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1951; 2177
    CP6/W/13 - CP6/W/24
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1951; 2177
    CPS/1 - CPS/SR.14
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1948; 2177
    1/1 - 1/62
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1949; 2177
    Annecy protoe
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1962; 2177
    BOP/1 - BOP/15
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1962; 2178
    BOP/16 - BOP/32
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1951; 2178
    MN (crazygang) Torquay
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1951; 2178
    MN.1 - MN/WP.6
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950; 2178
    MN/SR/1 - MN/SR/11
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1964; 2179
    COT/STAT/1 - CCT/STAT/22
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1962-1963; 2180
    COT/W1 - COT/W.22
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1949; 2180
    CP.2 Spaans
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1948-1949; 2180
    ICITO/1/1 - ICITO/1/20
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1953-1955; 2180
    Secret 1 - Secret 35
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1955-1957; 2181
    Secret 36-Secret 83
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1949-1951; 2182
    Secret/CP/1 - Secret/CP/19
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1949-1960; 2182
    Comm. III.12 - Comm. III.29
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1960-1961; 2183
    Comm. III.30 - Comm. III.52
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1961-1962; 2184
    Comm. III.53 - Comm. III.72
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1962-1963; 2185
    Comm. III.73 - Comm. III.124
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1959-1960; 2185
    Comm. III.3 - Comm. III.7
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1960; 2186
    Comm. III.7 - Comm. III. 11
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1959; 2186
    Comm. III/W2 A - Comm. III/W2 T
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1959; 2187
    Comm. III/W3 - Comm. III/W8 T
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1959; 2188
    Comm. III/W9 - Comm. III/W
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1952-1955; 2189
    CP/INF 17 - CP/INF 27
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT) International Monetary Fund., 1950; 2189
    Secretimp. restr. Australia
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950; 2189
    Secretimp. restr. Ceylon
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950; 2189
    Secretimp. restr. Chile
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950; 2189
    Secretimp. restr. India
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950; 2189
    Secretimp. restr. Pakistan
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950; 2189
    Secretimp. restr. Rhodesia
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950; 2189
    International. F. Secret INP restr. New
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1950; 2189
    Sealand Secretimp. United Kingdom
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade (GATT)., 1952-1953; 2190
    International Monetary Fund
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1963-1964; 2222
    AC/SC 1 - 14
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1962-1967; 2222
    C/19 - 75
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1960-1963; 2222
    C/INF/1-14
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1962-1967; 2222
    C/W/ 32 - 119
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1965-1967; 2223
    CM/ 24 - 43
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1964; 2223
    BOP/ 33 - 44
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1965; 2223
    BOP/ 45 - 55
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1966; 2224
    BOP/ 56 - 65
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1967; 2224
    BOP/ 66 - 76
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1962-1964; 2224
    BOP/INF/1 - 6
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1965-1967; 2224
    BOP/W/ 1 - 5
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1966; 2224
    BOP/R/ 1 - 6
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1967; 2225
    BOP/R 7 - 18
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1963-1964; 2225
    COT/ 1 - 40
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1964-1967; 2226
    COT/40 - 88
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1963-1964; 2226
    COT/INF/1 en 2
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1962-1966; 2226
    COT/M/ 1 - 6
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1965; 2226
    COT/Stat/ 1 - 25
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1965-1966; 2227
    COT/Stat/ 25 - 47
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1966; 2228
    COT/Stat/ 48 - 72
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1967; 2229
    COT/Stat/ 73 - 93
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1965-1967; 2230
    COT/W/ 48 - 89
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1962-1963; 2230
    W/62 1 en 2
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1962-1963; 2230
    W/63 1 - 13
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1963-1965; 2231
    Comm/2/ 135 - 141
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1959-1962; 2231
    Comm/2/ 1 - 12
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1959-1965; 2231
    Comm/2/W 2 - 11
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1961-1964; 2231
    Comm/3/W 14 - 19
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1965-1967; 2232
    W/65/ 1 - 7
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1965; 2232
    SR-index tot 11 SR/22 1 - 11
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1960; 2232
    SEVENTEEN 1 - 6
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1961; 2232
    EIGHTEEN 1 - 6
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1959; 2232
    COM/1/ 1 - 4
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1964; 2233
    COM/III/124 - 137
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1959-1963; 2233
    COM/III/INF/1 - 11
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1963-1964; 2233
    PRESS RELEASE 697 - 913
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1965; 2233
    PRESS RELEASE 914 - 946
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1966; 2234
    PRESS RELEASE 947 - 973
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1967; 2234
    PRESS RELEASE 974 - 1015
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1960-1961; 2234
    T.N./60/1 - 18
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1962; 2234
    T.N./60/SR/ 15 - 17
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1960-1961; 2234
    TN 60/W 1 - 29
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1963-1964; 2235
    TN/64/ 1 - 36
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1963-1964; 2235
    TN/64/AGRI/INF/ 1 en 2
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1964-1965; 2235
    TN/64/AGRI/ 1 - 5
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1964-1965; 2235
    TN/64/AGRI 4 en 7
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1965-1966; 2235
    TN/64/DP/4-16
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1963-1964; 2235
    TN/64/ZDC/ 1 - 27
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1964-1966; 2235
    TN/64/LDC/ 24 - 39
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1967; 2235
    TN/64/LDC/40
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1963-1964; 2236
    TN/64/NP/ 1 - 17
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1963-1964; 2236
    TN/64/NP/INF/ 1 - 3
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1963-1966; 2236
    TN/64/NTB/1 - 42
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1963; 2236
    TN/64/NTB/INF 1-
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1966; 2236
    TN/64/NTB/W/1 - 14
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1963-1966; 2236
    TN/64/SR/ 1 - 13
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1967; 2236
    TN/64/SR 15 en 16
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1965; 2236
    TN/64/TP/ 1 - 7
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1965-1966; 2236
    TN/64/TP/W/ 1 - 4
  - General Agreement on Tariffs and Trade., 1963; 2236
    TNC/INF/ 1 - 3
  - KENNEDY RONDE., 1962-1965; 517
  - KENNEDY RONDE., 1962-1965; 518
  - GATT DOC./COM/TD/C/W/1-7 - COM/TD/G/W/1., 1965-1966; 519
  - GATT DOC./INF/3 - INF/65/76., 1950-1959; 520
  - GATT DOC./INF/77 - INF/109., 1960-1964; 521
  - GATT DOC./SECR./38-119., 1955-1958; 522
  - GATT/TN/64/DP/W., 1965-1966; 523
  - GATT/TN/64/ME/W., 1965-1966; 523
  - GATT/TN/64/SECR/W., 1964; 523
  - GATT/W.22/SPEC./2SS/SR., 1964-1966; 524
  - JAARLIJKSE RAPPORTEN BETREFFENDE INTERNATIONALE HANDEL., 1966-1968; 525
  - COMITÉ SPÉCIAL DE L'ARTICLET111., 1969; 525
- UNITED NATIONS CONFERENCE ON TRADE AND EMPLOYMENT (UNCTE), 1947-1948
  - Preparatory Committee of the United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment at London., Preparatory Committee of the United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment at Lake Succes.; Preparatory Committee of the United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment at Genève.; 1947; 2260
  - Preparatory Committee of the United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment at Genève., 1947; 2261
    E/PC/T 139-210
  - Preparatory Committee of the United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment at Genève., 1947; 2262
    E/PC/T 139-210 Journal E/PC/TPV 2
  - Preparatory Committee of the United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment at Genève., 1947; 2263
    E/PC/T/INF
  - Preparatory Committee of the United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment at Genève., 1947; 2264
    E/PC/T/DEL
    E/PC/T/EC
    E/PC/T/TAC/SR
    E/PC/TRF
  - Preparatory Committee of the United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment at Genève., 1947; 2265
    E/PC/T/W/1-132
  - Preparatory Committee of the United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment at Genève., 1947; 2266
    E/PC/T/V/133-344
  - Preparatory Committee of the United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment at Genève., 1947; 2267
    E/PC/T/A/SR
    E/PC/T/B/SR
  - Preparatory Committee of the United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment at Genève., 1947; 2268
    E/PC/T/C I-V
    E/PC/T/W I
  - Preparatory Committee of the United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment at Genève., 1947; 2269
    E/TC/T/C 6
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment., 1947-1948; 2270
    E/Conf. 2/SR
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment., 1947-1948; 2271
    E/Conf. 2/INF
  - United Nations Conference., 1947-1948; 2272
    E/Conf. 2/C 1
    E/Conf. 2/C.1 /SR
    E/Conf. 2/C.1/W
    E/Conf. 2/C.1 /C
    E/Conf. 2/C. 2 & 3/A
    E/Conf. 2/C. 2 & 3/A/W
    E/Conf. 2/C. 2 & 6/A
    E/Conf. 2/C. 2 & 6/A/W
    E/Conf. 2/C. 2 & 6/W
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment Havana 21 nov. '47 t/m 24 mrt. '48., 1947-1948; 2273
    E/Conf. 2/C. 2
    E/Conf. 2/C. 2 SR
    E/Conf. 2/C. A
    E/Conf. 2/C. 2/B
    E/Conf. 2/C. 2/B/W
    E/Conf. 2/C. 2/O
    E/Conf. 2/C. 2D/W
    E/Conf. 2/C. 2/C
    E/Conf. 2/C. 2/C/W
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment Havana 21 nov. '47 t/m 24 mrt. '48., 1947-1948; 2274
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment Havana 21 nov. '47 t/m 24 mrt. '48., 1947-1948; 2275
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3/SR
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3/A
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3/A/W
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment Havana 21 nov. '47 t/m 24 mrt. '48., 1947-1948; 2276
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3/B
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3/B/W
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3/C
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3/C/W
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3/D
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3/D/W
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3/E
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3/E/W
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3/F
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3/F/W
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3/G
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3/G/W
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3/H
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3/H/W
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3/J
    E/Conf. 2/C. 3/J/W
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment Havana 21 nov. '47 t/m 24 mrt. '48., 1947-1948; 2277
    E/Conf. 2/C. 4
    E/Conf. 2/C. 4/SR
    E/Conf. 2/C. 4/A
    E/Conf. 2/C. 4/A/W
    E/Conf. 2/C. 5
    E/Conf. 2/C. 5/SR
    E/Conf. 2/C. 5/W
    E/Conf. 2/C. 5/A
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment Havana 21 nov. '47 t/m 24 mrt. '48., 1947-1948; 2278
    E/Conf. 2/C. 6
    E/Conf. 2/C. 6/SR
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment Havana 21 nov. '47 t/m 24 mrt. '48., 1947-1948; 2279
    E/Conf. 2/C. 6/W
    E/Conf. 2/C. 7
    E/Conf. 2/C. 8
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Employment Havana 21 nov. '47 t/m 24 mrt. '48., 1947-1948; 2280
    E/Conf. 2/Bur
    E/Conf. 2Bur/SR
- UNITED NATIONS CONFERENCE ON TRADE AND DEVELOPMENT (UNCTAD).
  Opgericht in 1964 ter bevordering van de internationale handel en de algemene economische ontwikkeling.
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1820
    UNCTAD
    E/Conf. 46 nr. 1 - 6
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1821
    E/Conf. 46 nr. 7 - 12
  - United Nations Conference on Trade and Development., 1964; 1822
    E/Conf. 46 nr. 13 - 31